Yes, boss, hello
Yes, hello
Ah, we're almost there, yes, yes, yes
- Hello
- Yes, hello.
Huh? boss
How is Lisian doing today?
- Uh, is this Lisian?
- Yes
- Is it 7,000 won?
- Hello, uncle
- Oh, are you here?
It's perfect
Oh, it's mine.
yes, thank you, thank you
Thank you, thank you for your hard work
Thank you, boss, thank you.
Best Actor Award
Seon Woo-hae from the movie ‘Ewha, Wolbaek’!
He's 11 years old, the youngest!
Driver, please sit here.
Yes, my name is Seonwoohae.
Where are you?
Have you ever been a child actor?
Seon Woo-hae...
Oh, no, no, wait a minute.
Hey, just say a little bit.
Please listen, teacher.
Try changing it
Hello, that director, Jin So-ra...
Did you hang up?
They say they don’t even listen to the planning.
I don't get it, huh?
Let's find out
Up to the threshold of recruitment
Let's put it on, this time
This is the editing scene for ‘Femicide for Love’
Please check
Yes, assistant director.
Oh, two hours before filming
What if you send me a crystal god?
Also, it wasn't just us who got it late, right?
The salad I ordered to-go arrived.
Okay, I'll see you there.
Yes!
thank you
- Hello
In the crystal scene
He changed into white clothes again.
In front of a woman with white trauma
A man who keeps wearing white clothes
Is this a romance or a thriller?
It’s a thriller, right?
It'll be like that until the end of filming, okay?
It's not like rewriting people.
Oh, don't rub it.
Thank you
It's really hateful
Uh, I'm near a traffic light, where am I?
Uh, we're at the intersection.
Where do you burn it?
uh? Uh, I see it.
uh
I'm here across the street
I can get on right away.
Uh, hey, hey, this
I saved it, I saved it
uh
- Oh my, what should I do?
-Are you okay?
Well, that's just
Just going, that car
-Are you okay?
- Oh my, what should I do?
- What should I do?
- Alcohol...
- Wake up.
- Let's go to the hospital first, yeah.
- Hospital?
Oh, I'm so drunk
I told you to go to the hospital first.
Are you okay?
wait
- Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work
- Taerin
- Huh?
Let's go to the car first
Let me just finish one thing and leave work.
- Okay.
- Yes
Um, Director Yang?
Do you have a moment?
hey! Are you crazy?
This idiot
Who are you trying to catch?
- Get off, when I say it.
- What?
Ana, you bastard.
Wait for you, you bastard.
Hey, if you don't say it
What are you going to do?
What are you going to do, you bastard!
I follow the traffic laws
I hope you comply.
This little bastard, this
Huh? Hey, did you avoid it?
아, 이 새끼, 그래, 그래
피하지 마, 이 새끼야
이제부터, 알았어?
This bastard, this
Hey, you bastard!
kid!
me, teacher
with me
Do you want to go to the police station or
Do you want to go and apologize?
I wish we could do both together
No, let’s move on smoothly, bro.
So my brother always
I'm not living at a loss.
I can't get those drinks right now.
But this is Seokju’s car.
Can I just drive like this?
It's not even Seok-ju, are you doing this?
That's what you care about now...
Anyway
The store opens a little early today
The cost of alcohol that I broke without being able to sell it
Don't you have to fill it up?
This miser
Are you honestly thinking about the price?
You chased it and caught it, right?
Hehe, that
How could that...
I'm stating the obvious
The costume team followed the original print.
I heard you prepared with black clothes.
I have to follow the script.
The author used white clothes in his prints.
I changed it brazenly
In this episode
It's the best sequence
If you do well, the main characters
He is a god who lives for everyone.
Just trying to look pretty
Because of one of you actors
Looks like it's all eaten up?
Oh my, if someone sees it
I think Mo Tae-rin is the main character, huh?
On the topic that was subbed as an option for Yeoju
Hey, the clothes were black until a month ago.
It suddenly turned white today
It's even a connection scene.
It's the same scene, but the clothes suddenly change
Does it make sense to wear white clothes?
I'm not the only one with this problem
Did the author get shot in the head?
- hey!
- why!
My brother said he wanted to eat curry
I have to go buy some curry too.
Are you going to do this too, really?
Don't blur the context
Are we talking about curry?
Wait a minute
Oh, did curry come out?
yes, let's go now
Hey, Jeyeon
Still assistant director, scripter, FD
Everyone made a fuss about me
But what should I do? My brother insists.
I'm dying too
It's all just about me
What are you saying to me?
Even if it’s just pretending to persuade
Try it out
Anyway, I'll go.
Curry that
Just one tap of the elbow
I think it will work
Oh no
- I'll go.
- Go
Let's go
Tuk
Spill curry on your clothes
shed it
Waist!
head!
curry!
On clothes! curry!
Spill it! Bury it!
Spill it! Bury it! On clothes!
I like curry
curry
Mmm, so delicious
Mmm, curry, curry
Hey
- Yes?
- It's white clothes.
Oh, I'm sorry, bro, I...
be careful
Ah...
Wow, this
I only have one white outfit, ah, this...
Let's go first
Goodbye, Seong Je-yeon
Aren't you guys going?
Nam Joon-ho, I just didn’t have a prepared costume.
Return to original costume
He said he spilled curry on his clothes.
What is it
Jeyeon, me again today
The meeting got longer
I don't think I can see you, sorry
Off work now!
Are you not even sleeping?
It's 3 in the morning, hey
Wow, you waited until this time?
At that time, PD Yoo Jeil’s professional show
Even if it’s a one-off appearance, it’s okay.
How can I get a seat?
Wow, the CEO also mentioned it today.
I tried to do it in advance
The most senior is now
I'm busy looking for some kind of novelist.
Just in case, that novelist
Do your homework
I see that you look for things you can forget
I guess he likes it quite a bit.
What's your name, the novelist?
Jin Moo-young
Ah, I read it in college.
I was really shocked, but it was refreshing
I understand first of all
Then
Pilot preparing for seniors
There's no tip for Taryn, really?
you
Are you going to do this every quarter?
What, did you leave it to me?
That feeling of not being able to find anyone
You know?
Who on earth are you looking for like that?
Let me help you
If you are going to Motaerin
I only have a plan to connect with Seonwoohae.
It fell down last year
the plan
Do you still have regrets?
Jeyeonah
Because you stepped up
Would you like to come look for Seonwoo?
Then I am the most senior
Introduce it right away
Really?
Is it real?
Do you need to buy flowers?
What’s wrong with getting dumped at this age?
I don't know if my teeth are grinding so hard
Huh?
Ah
One day I cried
One day I cursed like a fire
At the end
You wanted to see it, I guess?
Do you still remember that?
Forget it, please
Turning twenty
It's my first time drinking alcohol
Crying senior?
It's so provocative
But why is Seonwoohae suddenly?
Ah
A plan that collapsed last year
Are you talking about it again?
No, no, not yet.
I don't know yet
Someone posted this on my feed before
No matter how you look at it, I think it's true
It's a bit difficult to get there
When I was in high school, I used to talk rudely.
I was a kid who lived hard.
Treated like cheap
Just pretend you're not a senior
Dress up and go
Should I add a beard?
Can you do it?
No, should I just check the business location?
Sora senior can do the recruiting.
Go find it and hit it
Seonwoohae is right
Do you think you'll appear?
I don't think I would do it if it were me
Not like that with your senior.
You know what I'm saying
You will be reluctant
I had a job when I was young.
But you treated me like a cheap person?
If I refuse this time, it's because of my senior.
Me?
Don’t ever pretend to know me again!
forever!
Isn't it open for business?
guest
Welcome
I think I need to buy a flower pot.
Ah
If you want to buy it
I think you should buy it.
That's right
Let's go in
What, you don't recognize me
I...
By potted plants, you are talking about plants, right?
Well...
Maybe? That...
Something easy to manage
If you leave it alone, it will grow on its own, something like that.
yes
Seong Je-yeon
I still
Don't you act like you know?
Uh...
Huh?
Is it positive or negative?
Nice to meet you
How are you?
That...
Do you know Mo Tae-rin?
I am a manager
I came today for a casting call.
I don't know
Why don’t you know our Taerin?
Yo
The two of you are national brother and sister
You were very famous.
He was also a classmate from the same high school.
Ah
With a mediocre number of alumni
I guess you were asked to do some casting.
Regarding the sitcom you did as a child actor
There is a PD you are looking for.
Through Mo Tae-rin and Seon Woo-hae
Nostalgia of those days
Living in the present, something like that...
When it airs
You can also promote your store here.
A reunion of grown-up siblings
It's so heartbreaking
How did Seonwoohae grow up?
You'll be curious
I miss you
I can guess why you're reluctant.
It's not a bad plan.
If you could please review...
What is the reason you are guessing?
How much do you pay if you go out there?
admission fee
I wonder how much it was set
The expression is a bit...
No, lock them in a cage somewhere
It's not like I'm going to film it.
The past that ended brightly
Indebted to Mr. Motae-rin
There is no reason to appear
People whose faces I don't even know
Sell your memories
They tell me to put on display my life, which is nothing special.
Yeah, well, like that.
Maybe you heard it
Isn’t it a bit of a leap?
I think you're displeased with something
I don’t want to go out there because I like it.
Let's say you have a busy life.
Have you ever
when i was in high school
Is this because they treat me like a cheap person?
I'm sorry if you hurt me
i apologize
you
Have you ever treated me like I was cheap?
That...
Please help me just this once
What does it mean to like a classmate?
Is this okay, a flower pot?
please do something
Why not?
How do you move?
I do it by car
I won't take any money
Because you wasted your time getting here
Don't be comfortable speaking vaguely.
Did you miss me too?
How did I grow up?
I understand your intention to refuse.
hello there
Ah, I pretended to know first.
I should have hit first
- Uh
- Ah, I was pushed by the momentum, I
Hey, can you hear me? Who are you talking to?
No, when I think about it
I went that far a long time ago
I don't think I said anything rude.
What are you talking about, all of a sudden?
Oh, I'm so sleepy.
I just met Seonwoo-hae.
- What?
- He said he doesn't, he appears.
Hey!
Without me knowing...
No, I met him in person...
Where did you meet?
Information on people who do not wish to appear
It's hard to just tell you like that...
Seong Je-yeon
Are you putting me on medication? uh?
- The will seemed firm...
- Where are you? Seong Je-yeon!
No, no, why are you yelling?
No, because of my senior.
I'm the one who's embarrassed to death
No, I'm not angry.
It's because I'm so upset, I'm upset
CEO, what should I do if I can’t eat?
Uh, I have dinner plans.
Are you here?
Did you have a good meeting?
book? Review of the original work? Is it fun?
Jin Moo-young?
Producer Jeil Yoo was looking for this person.
Are you saying you're desperate?
I heard people talking around the neighborhood.
yes, that's right
To create a common topic
Because it’s good to know
But I'm kind of used to it
I don't read novels
Is finding a novelist a big deal?
Yes, this is Kim Pil-du.
I checked through the publisher.
appoint an agent
It looks like he's hiding...
What is it?
Oh my, my heart
Oh my, oh my, I'm sorry
Director, here, the heart is on the left.
Wait, I
I'm leaving work
I have something to check.
I'll go first, sorry.
Oh, that's right!
damn
What is this?
Wish bracelet
I bought it because I wanted to give it to you
But why is it still...
1 service
cactus
The problem is that coincidences are always unexpected.
In reality, why isn't there a trailer?
Did you see the bulletin board?
Listener who read aloud earlier
There's a fuss about who it is, huh?
I really like my junior’s voice
‘A small stone
'I just fell in'
‘Everything poured out’
'In his name
'It's raining too much'
‘They said the fortune teller was chilly’
'Your weather is
'I hope it's all good'
‘He has been obese his whole life.
The smiling face'
‘I don’t remember very well’
'In his name
What made the garden
'Your life'
'To become clear
'It was raining'
‘It was because I wanted to convey’
‘That’s when I realized’
What is this voice?
'Voice of the day'
By inviting listeners
There is a reading corner
‘Voice of the day’?
'The fact that I forgot him
'I forgot'
I think that's right
yes
Oh, yes, I got a call.
Yeah, I'll see you later, yeah
Yes, hello?
Yes, this is the lobby.
I can't get access authenticated.
Yes, where are you?
Because it's the lobby.
No, where are you from?
Hannah Bang sent flowers.
Oh, yes, I'm going down.
Hey
The director said it was your first radio.
I guess you sent flowers
I'll take it
- Then I'll go in first.
- Yeah, over there.
'What if'
'If you exist in another world'
‘I hope you understand my wishes’
'I hope it's sunny all the time there'
‘It was a small wish and faith’
'Beautiful morning' so far
It was ‘Today’s Voice’
I will listen to the music and then come to part 4.
The guest is actress Mo Tae-rin.
Taerin, why are you crying?
Are you nervous because it’s your first time on the radio?
Why do I remember that time?
I don't know
It's okay, okay?
Thank you for your hard work
- Senior
- Huh?
I'm leaving work
Oh, what is it?
What is it, I'm really sick
Go away
Please call me next time
When listeners get bored
Buy me a drink
hello
- I'll go.
- Yes, thank you for your hard work.
Did you cry?
yes
Why are you crying?
Why are you smiling?
Because it’s pretty?
Ah, I understand.
This time I laughed because it was funny.
That
Don't you know?
Who doesn’t know Mo Tae-rin?
Yes, this is Seokju Kim.
That's right, Kim Seok-ju
Are you saying you know or don’t know?
hello
I came down after receiving a call.
You can give it to me
Is this a coincidence?
Why are you speaking informally?
Are you pretending not to know again?
Because you declined that invitation?
No.
Why are you smiling?
Because I’m glad to see you
Let me take a picture of you holding flowers.
Photo, why?
Send it to Hannah Bang
Delivery completion proof shot
Okay, let's take a picture.
Do you still like your brother?
Did you turn?
Oh, I guess I'll have to film it again.
No, no
I received it well
I'll tell you
Please delete the photos taken with him.
thank you
What concept is this, you two?
Why at the broadcasting station? Flower delivery?
So then, did you come to debut?
if again
They said they would let you debut, are you going to do it?
You and Seong Je-yeon
Did you keep watching it even after you graduated?
Or
Did he study abroad like you?
He couldn't go because his house was broke.
When my brother debuts, he’ll do it in a big way
Should I send you a flower basket?
Buy the flower basket from my store
What, where are you going?
Are you going to debut?
Okay, okay, fighting!
cactus
Cactus?
Cactus what?
No, I gave it to you then.
Did you just kill him?
Ah, me again
Even now
I thought you wanted to appear
Business done?
That...
Did you take my number earlier? Contact me
Why me?
What is the reason?
There's a problem with the cactus
I'm hungry
I did something
What is this?
water in a paper cup
Just give that much once a month.
Say it, it's fast
As I got older, I started doodling...
To waste time
What a trick?
like!
'like'?
Ah
Get better?
It's still blowing like that
- Thank you
-Nothing to say
- Senior
- Huh?
Someone laughed at me earlier
Why did you laugh? Was she really pretty?
Hey
Huh?
How can I not laugh when I see you?
As long as you don't get a puncture on your head
Wait a minute
Did you cry?
Are your eyes red?
just
I soaked it a little because it reminded me of the old days.
What are you thinking?
Um...
Thought I wanted to die
What?
Oh, just kidding.
- Are you thinking a lot these days?
- No
It won't work, you
Let's go to the mountains with me tomorrow
- Oh, I don't like it.
- Come with me.
- I don't like it!
- Go, Mr. Motaerin.
Jeyeon, I have a long meeting.
I don't think I'll see you today
It's okay, assistant director.
Please contact me again anytime
Hello, PD Jeil Yoo.
I am the manager of actress Mo Tae-rin.
Yes, yes
I am your junior.
Seoul National University Management
As I said
The manager who graduated from Seoul National University
It's my first time seeing you again
Jin Mu-young's novel
I heard you like it
Maybe it's because he's a classmate of mine
It was nice to meet you, for no reason
We went to the same high school
Ah
Are you close? Are you still in contact?
yes, what
finish
That's how it's happening
Can you make some space?
Still, better than strangers
My classmate is affectionate and goes well.
That's right, that's right
Jeongi
Is there one?
Is it affectionate?
Why are you smiling?
Because I’m glad to see you
like that
Even if it seems
When you're done, go quickly
How many minutes do you meditate?
I just confiscated my face
I need to use that number, director.
Turn off the fire
I have now accumulated achievements
Some salary...
I really turned it off
- I really feel like I can do it now.
- Oh! Are you in good condition?
Are you okay?
take some air
Too good?
Taerin, look here.
Wow, it's hot
Thank you
Good thing you came out
That's right
What is Jin Moo-young?
Number of PD Yoo Jeil meetings to be held
This time, Yoo Jeil
Seon Woo-hae’s casting failed?
Well, I read novels
Because I summarized everything
After understanding it well
When we meet later
Naturally, you know?
There must be a common topic in conversation.
Producer Yoo is really going to use me.
Even the kids who say it’s long
I'm standing in line
Producer Yoo Je-il is
Even if it's a one-off, where is it?
It would be better if it was fixed every week.
If you try to drink it all you will end up feeling flat.
Let’s go down the mountain and eat something delicious.
Mmm, sounds delicious.
Makgeolli
Can I order it?
Makgeolli is a carbohydrate.
How sweet and delicious is it?
Order it, let’s eat it.
I won't eat it
I didn’t use salted shrimp and wrapped it with a lot of ssam.
I will eat mainly lean meat
Taerin
You don’t want to do entertainment, right?
just
I'm not confident
Showing my true self
I'm not even funny
You're fun, don't worry
To raise public awareness
There's no such thing as entertainment.
Oh, I hate you
I don't want to force it either, man.
You look just like my mom
That I don't want to do it
I made you do it anyway, for my own sake.
I never had a daughter like you
It's too much, Mom.
So now all that's left is
Jin Moo-young in front of PD Yoo
I'm taking you there
Is it Jin Moo-young?
How about crying in front of him?
When I cried when I was young
Everyone listens to me
Are you really going to give a quick answer?
But
Would you listen to it even if you were thirty-four?
Listen...
I will do it, in a different way.
Is there no way?
Why aren't you answering the phone like this?
Oh, what a surprise.
What is it? Why are you here?
Even informal greetings are shared
I guess I don’t have a rank yet.
What did you say? Henchman?
Team leader
Since when did you start coming in and out?
From today
Since it's a recession these days, I'm planning to work two jobs.
You're laughing
Aren’t you taking over our company?
Well, it’s not a business class or anything, is it?
Why do you want me to debut
Don't you think it would have come?
under! It's so funny, are you a comedian?
Hello, CEO
Seokju Why are you here?
Now, let’s do some work at work
I think it's time to learn
When my son comes to be my boss
Is our team leader leaving the company?
Don't go anywhere, CEO.
Ah, what about PD Yoo?
Was it due to school ties? You're at Seoul National University.
Well, to be exact, I dropped out.
Although I rubbed it
For that, I went to Seoul National University...
Go carefully
Is it okay to look forward to entertainment?
If that is also Yoo Je-il
I will try my best to make it
Yes, PD.
Yes, this is Yoo Je-il.
Have you set a date?
Ah, my daughter is starting next week.
I need to prepare for the exam
Ah, the PD’s daughter is also a fan.
Ah, your daughter is a fan.
Yes, yes, you are.
I'll catch up with you as soon as possible, yes.
Phone calls that don't pay
You're not accepting it, are you?
If you don't receive it, I'll really go looking for it.
Ah, why does he keep
Are you putting it the other way?
- Oh, did you call me?
- Uh
Some flowers inside too
You said you wanted to leave it?
Ah, hello
You can talk to this guy.
- Have a hard time
- Uh
Do you want to put fresh flowers inside the cafe?
- Yes
- Ah
If you want to place flowers,
How about preserved flowers?
It has a bit of a fresh flower feel to it
Preserve, what is that?
That...
Oh, this guy is in business again.
That's really...
- Wait a minute, I'll show you.
- Yes
Usually hydrangeas
I use a lot of roses.
If you look at it, it looks like this...
- Wait a minute, sorry.
- Yes
Wait a minute
Yes, hello?
I finally got it
Where are you?
They told me to contact them
Not receiving contact
Isn’t it a bit much?
why?
What, is there a problem with the cactus?
I see you are empty-handed
I don’t think that’s the number of cases.
Are you hungry?
What do you think of people?
Would you say that, boss?
Who is looking for me if I have a number of cases?
uh? That...
Jin Moo-young
How could I have forgotten this?
Do you still have it?
This is a book I bought with my own money.
I can't throw it away
The bookstore where I bought this book has disappeared.
Is that bookstore gone?
The publisher that published this book is
They say it went bankrupt
Oh, you did it?
It's out of print and no longer available.
Yes, no
What's the point?
It's that kind of novel.
yet
I have fans, even high school students
Isn’t it so wonderful and heartbreaking?
once
Won't you meet me?
High school student?
Should I at least appeal with tears?
Yeah
give it a try
That's what it means
It's not a request to appear.
They say I'm just a fan
Can't it?
Yeah, let's meet, whatever.
So easy?
Can’t it be easy? What, make it difficult?
I like it because it's easy
Thank you for your hard work
Hey, let me help you.
Can I move this?
This must be heavy
I'm strong, really
You hurt your hand too
Okay
- It's in the three.
- Uh
Now, one, two!
why are you touching
What are you touching?
no
I decided to put it on three.
What if I lift it in two?
Ah...
I'm surprised, I'm surprised
No, why are you lifting it in two?
I'll do it
But why are your ears so red?
Are you open?
don't do it
No, what did I do?
- I think you're putting more into it.
- Oh, don't do it.
I'll do it
You go over there and rest.
A lot poured out
That's right
Well, now
Did you decide to pretend to know?
you are so real
Spit out everything you can
So honest
I think you did too, I remember
Ah, good
True
I wanted to live neatly
me too
Like that
Stop talking nonsense
Just clean it up, okay?
Ah, yes, director.
Yeah, yeah, I'm leaving now, yeah
I have to return now
Wait a minute
If you call me, please answer
Going
ah!
I'm afraid they'll say I won't do it again
I brought some bribes
Use it if you get hurt
Wow
This is my first time seeing such ugly gloves
My heart is pretty when I prepare gloves
Hold on
Going
I don't clean it up until the end.
Snacks are out
- thank you
- Enjoy your meal.
What's going on, you keep looking at your phone?
Flower shop SNS management
Wasn’t that what Nuri was doing?
Yeah
I have a call waiting for you
I'm afraid I'll get scolded again if I don't reach it.
Ugh, hey, I guess I have a dirty temper.
It's like that
There's a side to you that makes you do that.
Hold your phone carefully.
Yeah
Ah, I'll meet Jin Mooyoung's fan soon.
Ah... huh?
Why did you decide that, my doctor?
I'm your agent
don't worry
Because I'm going out myself
Then make money in the meantime
Why did you turn down all broadcast invitations?
Shhh, shh, shh, shh, shh
I thought you were going to call me
Saturday 2pm, meet at the cafe
I will attach a map for the location.
Are you awake?
Drink the juice, this
What kind of house do you work from?
Are you crazy about money?
Hey, Noori
Do people your age read books too?
book?
Why don't you look?
They say I have a fan
I think he's your age
Because it’s amazing
I also forgot
Did I write a book?
Oppa, I wanted to read it when I was young.
Didn’t you write a novel?
But for preschool children to read
Wasn’t the content a bit difficult?
Hey, you can set your own level.
Rather than writing childishly
Much better, whatever.
If I wrote it to be read
Should have been on my level
Oh my, every time I read that
Who was sleeping...
That's it, okay
Why?
If this breaks on its own
They say wishes come true
What on earth did you wish for?
It hasn't happened yet?
Listening well to what you say
This will never stop
It won't break, it won't break
It never breaks
Hey, you should hang out that laundry.
Yes, PD.
Oh, yes, it's okay.
Yes, yes, yes
Yes, please come slowly, yes
- Oh, are you here?
- Uh
What is that flower?
Oh, fan service?
It's yours
You liked this flower, long ago
Do I do this?
- What would you like to drink?
- Yes
Ah, the guests are late.
Because the car was so congested
Customers?
Ah, with the entertainment PD.
I'm coming with your daughter.
It won’t hurt if you know it too
no
The benefits are much greater, in many ways
But he has been in the industry for a long time.
You are Seonwoohae...
I don't know if you recognize me
It's pretty
I have a fan who wants to meet me
I'm an idiot for believing that
Huh?
Hey
Hey, where are you going?
What if I go like this?
In a place like this
I don’t think there’s any reason to stay any longer.
Could it be that I am your fan itself?
Do you think I lied?
Your fan is a minor and a high school student.
Is it strange to have a guardian with you?
It seems important that the guardian is a PD.
To Seong Je-yeon
I won't deny it
It was like that from the beginning.
I want it to be private
I guess I get it back like this
Among classmates I met after becoming a member of society
Where is the complete saga?
The construction is a total failure, what do you get in return?
Selling other people’s memories
I said I didn't want to be used
Selling my memories
Because I'm trying to use you
I want to come out as a writer
I told you clearly
What's the problem?
problem?
No problem, what's the problem?
To you I
Eat it for your work
Is it like a bubble?
No, well, it's nice to meet you
Can I at least unpack it?
What are we, to that extent
Was it a meaningful classmate?
If so
Do you believe it?
Oh my, my junior is here.
- Hello, PD.
- Welcome.
It's an occupational disease
Aren’t you secretly welcoming it?
Are you here?
What should I do?
Which one...
hello
This is Jin Muyoung, nice to meet you.
Yes, I am Yoo Je-il.
Because your spirit is so clear,
I guess you've been hiding it all this time, huh?
I am majoring in creative writing.
I'm preparing
The Korean language teacher also said I was talented.
If you go to university and learn
You said you would like it
Are you using a pen name?
Can I ask what your real name is?
Ah, dad
don't invade privacy
Maybe later
Could you take a look at my post?
For those who are busy
Well, are you asking for something like that?
If you need my opinion
I don't know if it will help...
It's too much, already!
Ah, but the novelist
What happened?
I wish it was at least a few thousand won, whatever.
I think I started with that in mind.
Well, why is it so great?
It didn't happen
Oh, Dad really...
I think it's a very novel reason.
I also want to make money by writing
I'm also going to participate in the daily contest.
Uh, this guy too
As long as you go to the hundred days that are said to be my best,
He was famous for winning awards.
Oh, that's right
You debuted when you were in high school, right?
How was it back then?
then
There was some atmosphere.
That's why everyone
difficult to approach easily
Well, there was something like that, right?
you
You didn't know, right?
I didn't know
But don’t they really look alike?
In the past, with Sunwoo Hae
You often hear things like that, right?
A bit like that friend
Doesn’t it look a little lacking?
I?
What on earth is Seonwoohae?
Stop acting like you're from the past
Why are you like this today?
I'm angry at my dad
Drop the pretense, stop, what's wrong?
I owe you a lot today
You said it was in charge of Mr. Taerin Mo, right?
Let's have a meeting
thank you
Thank you, goodbye.
It was nice to meet you
Please go in
A PD who tells you to your face and asks you to meet right away
You who receive it, indeed
Then you refuse to accept it right away?
While considering all of that
When do you work?
yes
I had a hard time imitating a good classmate.
The expression is a bit like that.
you meet me again
I don't think I've ever been happy
Let me ask you one thing.
The high school student's guardian earlier
Even if it wasn't PD
Would you have let me go just because you were my fan?
What do you want to say?
Just curious
Are you that kind of person?
just
Kids who shine like you
I'm curious about what you're dreaming about
What kind of person am I that you expected?
Thank you for staying today.
No matter how you were
I'm indebted anyway
Thank you for your time
I hope you prosper
yes
You too
That's right, I asked you to delete this.
It's worth asking for it to be deleted.
Take a good picture. What is this?
Hey, you go to the supermarket and buy some green onions.
While I was gone, I got some fresh air.
What kind of green onions are you buying?
You're so dazed
It's because it's annoying to look at
Because there are no customers now
Come back, it's okay
Go and get some air
- Have we run out?
- Uh
What kind of person am I that you expected?
what?
What is it really?
Why are you here?
Ah, that...
What to say
I don't think I did everything, earlier
So that's...
That flower from earlier
Because I cut the stem diagonally.
Just plug it in
Even without a vase
I think there are plastic bottles
Recycle
water once a day
Change it, make sure, uh
Are you here to talk about that?
uh
Well, that too
Well, I mean...
Are you Seonwoo?
Tell people to misunderstand
I'm having such a hard time, why?
What misunderstanding?
If you're with a man
It's perfect for misunderstanding
It's just like letting the company know about my private life...
Hey
-Why are you dressed like this?
- uh?
You're really strong...
I told you I was strong
what clothes are you wearing
Are you wearing something like this?
Doesn’t it disappear when it rains?
I've been wearing this for 10 years
It's economical
There's no such thing, right?
How do you know about the company?
You didn't mean to come find me, did you?
It wasn't
Ah...
Why did you come?
Even wearing an apron
There was no panic
Am I too promiscuous?
Not to that extent
we now
If you want
You can see it as much as you want, right?
Nope
What is it?
just
Greetings that it was nice to meet you
hello
Hey!
If it's nice to see you, I'll buy you some food
Alcohol too
I'm not even nineteen anymore